http://www.cisresearch.com/privacy-policy

Monday – Friday 8 am to 5pm
HomeAbout UsServicesTestimonialsMission & Value StatementVideo GalleryEnrolling StudiesGurnee, IL ClinicCardiovascular Disease & Diabetes ?GoutLow TestosteroneOsteoarthritis of the KneeType 2 Diabetes and Kidney DiseaseUncontrolled Blood PressureKenosha, WI ClinicCardiovascular Disease & Diabetes ?FibromyalgiaMigrainesOverweight with CV event or PAD?Uncontrolled Blood Pressure?RheumatologyAnkylosing Spondylitis/ Ankylosing SpondyloarthritisPatientsPatient QuestionnaireAbout Clinical StudiesSafety and ProtectionPreparing for Your VisitQuestions to AskHealth EducationAnkylosing SpondylitisArthritisAsthmaDepressionDiabetesFibromyalgiaGeneral AnxietyGoutHeart FailureHigh CholesterolHypertensionHypogonadismInfluenzaLow Back PainLupusMigrainesObesityOsteoarthritisOsteoarthritis of the KneePsoriatic ArthritisPSVTRheumatoid ArthritisPhysiciansAffiliate P.I.sPhysician QuestionnaireInvestigator BenefitsInvestigator RoleTherapeutic AreasSponsorsStudy ExperienceContact
Join a Trial
Privacy Policy
Breadcrumb
Home
Privacy Policy
Clinical Investigation Research, Inc. Website Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy was last modified on November 11, 2015.
Clinical Investigation Research, Inc. (CIS) ("us", "we", or "our") operates http://www.cisresearch.com (the "Site"). This page is intended to inform you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
We use your submitted Personal Information only for improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Information Collection And Use
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally, identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name, phone number ("Personal Information").
When and How Clinical Investigation Specialists, Inc. (CIS) May Contact You
When you register with Clinical Investigation Specialists, Inc.  or complete a prequalification questionnaire associated with a particular trial, you indicate your consent for CIS to store your Personal Information in our database and contact you about clinical trials for which you may be eligible by various means, including telephone, email, and US mail. You also have the option of receiving emails regarding new postings to our site, including news or new clinical trials.
Links to Third Party Sites
Our website includes links to other websites hosted by other entities (including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter) whose privacy practices may differ from those of CIS. If you submit personal information to any of those websites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit.
Information Sharing and Transfer
We may share your Personal Information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement or unless you expressly opt out to such sharing.
Service Providers/Partners
We may provide your information with third-party service providers (e.g., call centers, email service providers), or data partners who are contractually bound to handle your information confidentially and prohibited from disclosing your information to others.
Log Data
We do not currently collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our site. Some of our linked vendor site operators may collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit their site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information including, but not limited to, your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.
Cookies
We do not currently store Cookies to collect information.  Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Cookies may also be deleted by you, the user, from your computer.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, please be aware of the fact that that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
Clinical Investigation Specialists, Inc. may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us
Phone: 847-599-2492
Insert contact us at administrator@cisresearch.com
One discovery today may change the world tomorrow.
Clinical Investigation Specialists © 2011 / Our Privacy Policy
